Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- New York City Mayoral Personal Papers, 1965-1973; Part II
  - Robert W. Sweet (Deputy Mayor), 1969; Series XI; 6 linear feet (15 boxes)
    - Campaign Background-Subject
      - Civil Service Political Action Committee (Box 214, Folder 64)
      - Councilmatic district liaisons (Box 214, Folder 65)
      - Deficit committee (Box 214, Folder 66-67)
      - Election Reform Task Force (Box 214, Folder 68)
      - Finance (Box 214, Folder 69)
      - Local research projects (Box 214, Folder 70)
      - Medicare (Box 214, Folder 71)
      - Municipal archives (Box 214, Folder 72)
      - Office space (Box 214, Folder 73)
      - Opinion polls (Box 214, Folder 74)
      - Proportional representation (Box 214, Folder 75)
      - Puerto Rico, Lindsay committee (Box 215, Folder 76)
      - Raymond Street jail (Box 215, Folder 77)
      - Real Estate department (Box 215, Folder 78)
      - Registration campaign (Box 215, Folder 79)
      - Republican platform (Box 215, Folder 80)
      - Senator Charles Goodell (Box 215, Folder 81)
      - Senator Jacob K. Javits (Box 215, Folder 82)
      - Senator Charles H. Percy (Box 215, Folder 83)
      - State committeemen (Box 215, Folder 84)
      - Super cabinet members (Box 215, Folder 85)
      - Super cabinet minutes (Box 215, Folder 86)
      - Voting machines (Box 215, Folder 88)
      - Voter registration (Box 215, Folder 89-90)
    - Personnel, Recommendations and Resumes
      - Budget (Box 216, Folder 91)
      - Career Servants-Civil Service (Box 216, Folder 92)
      - Consultants (Box 216, Folder 93)
      - Data, resume (Box 216, Folder 94)
      - Expenses (Box 216, Folder 95)
      - Honorary appointments (Box 216, Folder 96)
      - Jobs filled (Box 216, Folder 97)
      - Jobs to be filled (Box 216, Folder 98)
      - Job trainees (Box 216, Folder 99)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda (Box 216, Folder 100-102)
      - Personnel, $10,000 and over (Box 217, Folder 103)
      - Personnel #1 correspondence, memoranda (Box 217, Folder 104-105)
      - Personnel #2 correspondence, memoranda (Box 217, Folder 106-107)
      - Personnel #3 correspondence, memoranda (Box 218, Folder 108-110)
      - Vacancy Control Board, agenda of (Box 218, Folder 111)
    - Personnel, Resumes and Appointments
      - Glidden, William T. (Box 219, Folder 112)
      - Papantonia, Edward (Box 219, Folder 113)
      - Riesel, Victor (Box 219, Folder 114)
      - Mayer, Harold (Box 219, Folder 115)
      - Banks, James (Box 219, Folder 116)
      - Sheffield, Joe (Box 219, Folder 117)
      - Finck, George (Box 219, Folder 118)
      - Spaulding, Asa T. (Box 219, Folder 119)
      - Davis, Edmund R. (Box 219, Folder 120)
      - Heyman, Henry (Box 219, Folder 121)
      - Turkel, Stanley (Box 219, Folder 122)
      - Robson, Morton S. (Box 219, Folder 123)
      - Perez, Captain Raman (Box 219, Folder 124)
      - Headly, Dorothy C. (Box 219, Folder 125)
      - Padilla, Dr. Elena (Box 219, Folder 126)
      - Mora, Angel Ruben (Box 219, Folder 127)
      - Schwartz, Michael W. (Box 219, Folder 128)
      - Schwadron, Jack (Box 219, Folder 129)
      - Montgomery, Nancy (Box 219, Folder 130)
      - Norris, Roy E. (Box 219, Folder 131)
      - Chin, Stanley L. (Box 219, Folder 132)
      - Cardone, Louis A. (Box 219, Folder 133)
      - Schaffer, Raymond (Box 219, Folder 134)
      - Tirbasso, Victor (Box 219, Folder 135)
      - Platt, Stoddard (Box 219, Folder 136)
      - Smith, Rev. Wesley (Box 219, Folder 137)
      - Ostrower, Donald A. (Box 219, Folder 138)
      - Krupsak, Mary Anne (Box 219, Folder 139)
      - Kress, Ralph H. (Box 219, Folder 140)
      - Lenzer, Robert L. (Box 219, Folder 141)
      - Holtzman, Elizabeth (Box 219, Folder 142)
      - Marr, Richard (Box 219, Folder 143)
      - Eaton, Douglas F. (Box 219, Folder 144)
      - Klein, Robert R. (Box 219, Folder 145)
      - Kaufman, Bill (Box 219, Folder 146)
      - Fusco, Dom (Box 219, Folder 147)
      - Lee, Charles (Box 219, Folder 148)
      - Lowe, Nolles (Box 219, Folder 149)
      - Deitch, Sue (Box 219, Folder 150)
      - Hogg, Charlotte C. (Box 219, Folder 151)
      - Hinckley, Walter J. (Box 219, Folder 152)
      - Hentel, Nat (Box 219, Folder 153)
      - Padnos, Michael (Box 219, Folder 154)
      - Page, John (Box 219, Folder 155)
      - Nixon, John (Box 219, Folder 156)
      - Janes, Nathanial M. (Box 219, Folder 157)
      - Salomon, Eric M. (Box 219, Folder 158)
      - Rotker, Seymore (Box 219, Folder 159)
      - Buschmann, Albert (Box 219, Folder 160)
      - Kamisky, David (Box 219, Folder 161)
      - Rosner, Sigmund (Box 219, Folder 162)
      - O'Conner, Aida C. (Box 219, Folder 163)
      - Wells, Clara (Box 219, Folder 164)
      - Zeidenstein, George P. (Box 219, Folder 165)
      - Davis, Caroline F. (Box 219, Folder 166)
      - Marks, Leah (Box 219, Folder 167)
      - Morse, Robert A. (Box 219, Folder 168)
      - Taras, Charles (Box 219, Folder 169)
      - Rothman, Leda (Box 219, Folder 170)
      - Peniston, W. Frederick (Box 219, Folder 171)
      - Rosenfeld, Arthur (Box 219, Folder 172)
      - Benson, Charles (Box 219, Folder 173)
      - Lieberman, Joseph A. (Box 219, Folder 174)
      - Heath, Curtis (Box 219, Folder 175)
      - Dixon, James P., M.D. (Box 219, Folder 176)
      - Taylor, Harry (Box 219, Folder 177)
      - Kirschenbaum, Stephen (Box 219, Folder 178)
      - Eastman, Elrich A. (Box 219, Folder 179)
      - Rosenberg, Robert (Box 219, Folder 180)
      - Gillies, Archibald L. (Box 219, Folder 181)
      - Victor, Charlane (Box 219, Folder 182)
      - Meistrell, Frank J. (Box 219, Folder 183)
      - Crawford, Robert W. (Box 219, Folder 184)
      - Malito Robert J. (Box 220, Folder 185)
      - Pierce, Burton A. (Box 220, Folder 186)
      - Pette, Nicholas M. (Box 220, Folder 187)
      - Slauson, Dr. John (Box 220, Folder 188)
      - Curtis, Joseph E. (Box 220, Folder 189)
      - Murray, James (Box 220, Folder 190)
      - Nitzburg, Arthur E. (Box 220, Folder 191)
      - Koskinen, John A. (Box 220, Folder 192)
      - Landino, Albert A. (Box 220, Folder 193)
      - Bagley, Chester (Box 220, Folder 194)
      - Randolph, James W. (Box 220, Folder 195)
      - Bramwell, Henry (Box 220, Folder 196)
      - Boen, Doyle F. (Box 220, Folder 197)
      - Nelson, Charles E. (Box 220, Folder 198)
      - Goodman, Edwin A. (Box 220, Folder 199)
      - Jackson, Stuart A. (Box 220, Folder 200)
      - Becker, Jerome M. (Box 220, Folder 201)
      - Schwalb, Morris (Box 220, Folder 202)
      - Ashcraft, Henry (Box 220, Folder 203)
      - Fiss, Owen (Box 220, Folder 204)
      - Searles, Joseph L. (Box 220, Folder 205)
      - Gregory, George, Jr. (Box 220, Folder 206)
      - Stone, Joseph (Box 220, Folder 207)
      - Feder, Nathan (Box 220, Folder 208)
      - Gibbons, Walter (Box 220, Folder 209)
      - Buffington, G.N. (Box 220, Folder 210)
      - Feldman, Melvin S. (Box 220, Folder 211)
      - Dretzin, William (Box 220, Folder 212)
      - Guzzetta, John A. (Box 220, Folder 213)
      - Wells, John A. (Box 220, Folder 214)
      - Fuss, Abraham (Box 220, Folder 215)
      - Hubbard, Thomas B. (Box 220, Folder 216)
      - Griffin, Gil (Box 220, Folder 217)
      - Smith, James W. (Box 220, Folder 218)
      - Walsh, Peter A. (Box 220, Folder 219)
      - Wood, Albert D. (Box 220, Folder 220)
      - Colgate, Gilbert C. (Box 220, Folder 221)
      - Martin, Frederick (Box 220, Folder 222)
      - Cuomo, Mario Matthew (Box 220, Folder 223)
      - Crowly, James G. (Box 220, Folder 224)
      - Kay, Stanley L. (Box 220, Folder 225)
      - Constantine, Costa (Box 220, Folder 226)
      - Powekk, Robert S., Jr. (Box 220, Folder 227)
      - Hershey, Allen (Box 220, Folder 228)
      - Sharpe, Alexander E., II (Box 220, Folder 229)
      - Thomas, Morgan (Box 220, Folder 230)
      - De Roos, John G. (Box 220, Folder 231)
      - Jennings, Edward B. (Box 220, Folder 232)
      - Gresse, Robert W. (Box 220, Folder 233)
      - Garvey, Daniel S. (Box 220, Folder 234)
      - Renola, Raymond (Box 220, Folder 235)
      - Liebman, Lance (Box 220, Folder 236)
      - Mollen, Milton (Box 220, Folder 237)
      - Berger, Rear Admiral Hubert E. (Box 220, Folder 238)
      - Nordon, John (Box 220, Folder 239)
      - Mittel, Robert E. (Box 220, Folder 240)
      - Hertz, Barbara V. (Box 220, Folder 241)
      - Galvin, Thomas F. (Box 220, Folder 242)
      - Lane, Donald F. (Box 220, Folder 243)
      - Fletcher, Stephen (Box 220, Folder 244)
      - Wallen, Rear Admiral Harry N. (Box 220, Folder 245)
      - Rawlins, Earl A. (Box 220, Folder 246)
      - Duchin, Ira (Box 220, Folder 247)
      - Groopman, Abraham (Box 220, Folder 248)
      - McVicker, Dr. Charles (Box 220, Folder 249)
      - Wellings, Dr. Stanley S. (Box 220, Folder 250)
      - Congress, Jerome M. (Box 220, Folder 251)
      - Shapiro, Herbert (Box 220, Folder 252)
      - Montgomery, James L. (Box 220, Folder 253)
      - Thompson, James D. (Box 220, Folder 254)
      - Kramer, Horace Z. (Box 220, Folder 255)
      - Laval (Box 220, Folder 256)
      - Beckman, James H. (Box 220, Folder 257)
      - Blaustein, Arthur I. (Box 221, Folder 258)
      - Barner, Evelyn (Box 221, Folder 259)
      - Manzo, Salvatore (Box 221, Folder 260)
      - Atwell, Richard (Box 221, Folder 261)
      - Babe, Thomas J., Jr. (Box 221, Folder 262)
      - Wasley, John S.W. (Box 221, Folder 263)
      - Streuli, Konrad (Box 221, Folder 264)
      - Royal, Robert (Box 221, Folder 265)
      - Burns, John M. (Box 221, Folder 266)
      - Abrams, Herbert W. (Box 221, Folder 267)
      - Ravitch, Richard (Box 221, Folder 268)
      - Rubano, Charles (Box 221, Folder 269)
      - Piscitelli, Peter A. (Box 221, Folder 270)
      - Kelly, William P., Jr. (Box 221, Folder 271)
      - Moody, Joseph (Box 221, Folder 272)
      - Fox, William A. (Box 221, Folder 273)
      - Jorge, Wilfred (Bill) (Box 221, Folder 274)
      - Lawrence, Morton B. (Box 221, Folder 275)
      - Waldgeir, Max (Box 221, Folder 276)
      - Diehl, Charles E. (Box 221, Folder 277)
      - Romm, Joseph (Box 221, Folder 278)
      - Davis, Ross (Box 221, Folder 279)
      - Chase, Gordon (Box 221, Folder 280)
      - Soriano, Dale (Box 221, Folder 281)
      - Sahlein, William J. (Box 221, Folder 282)
      - Hamlin, Dr. Robert H. (Box 221, Folder 283)
      - Duba, John G. (Box 221, Folder 284)
      - Karr, George (Box 221, Folder 285)
      - Abernathy, Caryl (Box 221, Folder 286)
      - Thompson, Lawrence L. (Box 221, Folder 287)
      - Clarke, John O'Brien (Box 221, Folder 288)
      - Alvarado, Ralph E. (Box 221, Folder 289)
      - Shainswit, Beatrice (Box 221, Folder 290)
      - Ockenden, Katherine (Box 221, Folder 291)
      - Garrison, John R. (Box 221, Folder 292)
      - Bleiman, Julius J. (Box 221, Folder 293)
      - Warren, Roger (Box 221, Folder 294)
      - Wertheimer, Fred M. (Box 221, Folder 295)
      - McKenna, Eugene (Box 221, Folder 296)
      - Mark, Rev. Dr. Julius (Box 221, Folder 297)
      - Salten, Dr. David G. (Box 221, Folder 298)
      - Greben, Seymore (Box 221, Folder 299)
      - Hodges, Virgil H. (Box 221, Folder 300)
      - Morreson, Ed (Box 221, Folder 301)
      - Weiser, Joseph J. (Box 221, Folder 302)
      - Wenner, D. Richard (Box 221, Folder 303)
      - Pena, Sergio S. (Box 221, Folder 304)
      - Jacobs, Harold M. (Box 221, Folder 305)
      - Klugsberg, Abraham H. (Box 221, Folder 306)
      - Bahn, Charles (Box 221, Folder 307)
      - Potter, Howard E. (Box 221, Folder 308)
      - Dixon, Lynn West (Box 221, Folder 309)
      - Henkin, Norman E. (Box 221, Folder 310)
      - Morsell, John A. (Box 221, Folder 311)
      - Ash, Mrs. Ann (Box 221, Folder 312)
      - Maguire, Gene A. (Box 221, Folder 313)
      - Jones, Madison S. (Box 221, Folder 314)
      - Myerson, Bess (Box 221, Folder 315)
      - Velella, Vincent J. (Box 221, Folder 316)
      - Lazarus, Simon, III (Box 221, Folder 317)
      - Davis, Alvin (Box 221, Folder 318)
      - Dechter, Hyman (Box 221, Folder 319)
      - Lewis, William (Box 221, Folder 320)
      - Duchenbury, Col. James A. (Box 221, Folder 321)
      - Myers, Raymond F. (Box 221, Folder 322)
      - Allee, Dennis H. (Box 222, Folder 323)
      - Berlew, F. Kingston (Box 222, Folder 324)
      - David, Preston (Box 222, Folder 325)
      - Padavan, Frank (Box 222, Folder 326)
      - Ryan, Herbert F. (Box 222, Folder 327)
      - Robinson, Gilbert A. (Box 222, Folder 328)
      - Polakoff, Moses (Box 222, Folder 329)
      - Barnes, Robert E. (Box 222, Folder 330)
      - Mercogliano, Louis R. (Box 222, Folder 331)
      - Baker, Harold F. (Box 222, Folder 332)
      - Coleman, Gerald R. (Box 222, Folder 333)
      - Palumbo, Alfred (Box 222, Folder 334)
      - Klapper, Mrs. Donald (Box 222, Folder 335)
      - Margolis, Joseph (Box 222, Folder 336)
      - Mangano, Constantino (Box 222, Folder 337)
      - Gold, Jay (Box 222, Folder 338)
      - Turelsky, Gerald J. (Box 222, Folder 339)
      - O'Rourke, Maurice J. (Box 222, Folder 340)
      - Solame, Stuart C. (Box 222, Folder 341)
      - Levine, Louis L. (Box 222, Folder 342)
      - Grant, Albert J. (Box 222, Folder 343)
      - Sullivan, DeWitt (Box 222, Folder 344)
      - Dean, John (Box 222, Folder 345)
      - Simons, Donald (Box 222, Folder 346)
      - Thornell, Dick (Box 222, Folder 347)
      - Patterson, John (Box 222, Folder 348)
      - Harris, Charlie (Box 222, Folder 349)
      - Rothwax, Harold (Box 222, Folder 350)
      - Yorkman, Fredrick A. (Box 222, Folder 351)
      - Masters, John J. (Box 222, Folder 352)
      - O'Neill, John T. (Box 222, Folder 353)
      - Ostrow, Marcia Kerr (Box 222, Folder 354)
      - Stringer, Ronald (Box 222, Folder 355)
      - Grebetz, Judah (Box 222, Folder 356)
      - Burstein, Sidney (Box 222, Folder 357)
      - Romer, Harold (Box 222, Folder 358)
      - Sack, Bernard (Box 222, Folder 359)
      - Koenig, Murray (Box 222, Folder 360)
      - Senes, David (Box 222, Folder 361)
      - Berg, David (Box 222, Folder 362)
      - Scott, Philip David (Box 222, Folder 363)
      - Trager, David G. (Box 222, Folder 364)
      - Kirchenbaum, Irving (Box 222, Folder 365)
      - Bettman, Lynn (Box 222, Folder 366)
      - Goldner, Leo (Box 222, Folder 367)
      - Heestand, Olin J. (Box 222, Folder 368)
      - Mantzoros, George (Box 222, Folder 369)
      - Chiusano, Michael, Jr. (Box 222, Folder 370)
      - Schechter, Joseph (Box 222, Folder 371)
      - Tessler, Harold (Box 222, Folder 372)
      - Weissberg, Frank (Box 222, Folder 373)
      - Wharton, Joan (Box 222, Folder 374)
      - Groat, William B. (Box 222, Folder 375)
      - Kafka, Malcom E. (Box 222, Folder 376)
      - Brecher, Morris (Box 222, Folder 377)
      - Loiti, Antonio J. (Box 222, Folder 378)
      - Henderson, Mrs. Hazel (Box 222, Folder 379)
      - Berman, Alfred (Box 222, Folder 380)
      - Velez, Ramon S. (Box 222, Folder 381)
      - Silberstein, Dr. Richard (Box 222, Folder 382)
      - Gulino, Louis T. (Box 222, Folder 383)
      - Klappholz, Rabbi Kurt (Box 222, Folder 384)
      - Horne, Wilfred N. (Box 222, Folder 385)
      - Botein, Hon. Bernard (Box 222, Folder 386)
      - Saypol, Dr. George M. (Box 222, Folder 387)
      - Norford, George (Box 222, Folder 388)
      - Mandelbaum, Michael (Box 222, Folder 389)
      - White, Lee (Box 222, Folder 390)
      - Siler, Joel J. (Box 222, Folder 391)
      - Johnson, Halden (Box 222, Folder 392)
      - Bader, Dick (Box 222, Folder 393)
      - Seltzer, Arnold S. (Box 222, Folder 394)
      - Liebowitz, Rheba (Box 222, Folder 395)
      - Kesner, Robert T. (Box 222, Folder 396)
      - Sopher, Hank (Box 222, Folder 397)
      - Lazar, Harold S. (Box 222, Folder 398)
      - Zumbo, Hannibal F. (Box 222, Folder 399)
      - Maloney, William P. (Box 222, Folder 400)
      - Linville, Robert W. (Box 222, Folder 401)
  - Richard R. Aurelio (Deputy Mayor), 1969-1972; Series XII; 6.5 linear feet (16 boxes)
    Series XII is sub-divided into four sections:
    Subject Files, 1969
    Subject Files, 1970-1972
    Memoranda File, 1971
    - Correspondence
      - A (Box 223, Folder 1)
      - B (Box 223, Folder 2)
      - C (Box 223, Folder 3)
      - D (Box 223, Folder 4)
      - E (Box 223, Folder 5)
      - F (Box 223, Folder 6)
      - G (Box 223, Folder 7)
      - H (Box 224, Folder 8)
      - I-J (Box 224, Folder 9)
      - K (Box 224, Folder 10)
      - L (Box 224, Folder 11)
      - M (Box 225, Folder 12)
      - N-O (Box 225, Folder 13)
      - P-Q (Box 225, Folder 14)
      - R (Box 225, Folder 15)
      - S (Box 225, Folder 16)
      - T (Box 225, Folder 17)
      - U-V (Box 225, Folder 18)
      - W (Box 225, Folder 19)
      - X-Z (Box 225, Folder 20)
    - Subject files, 1969
      - Adverse comments for fair ballot (Box 226, Folder 21)
      - Advertising agencies (Box 226, Folder 22)
      - Advertising agency expenditures (Box 226, Folder 23)
      - Advertising, radio and TV time, celebrities, skits (Box 226, Folder 24)
      - Albano account (Box 226, Folder 25)
      - Announcement of candidacy (Box 226, Folder 26)
      - Aurelio, public relations biography (Box 226, Folder 27)
      - Aurelio, personal (Box 226, Folder 28)
      - Appointments (Box 226, Folder 29)
      - Battle-Page Daily News (Box 226, Folder 30)
      - Borough coordinators (Box 226, Folder 31)
      - Browdy Benjamin, finance (Box 226, Folder 32)
      - Cambridge opinion studies (Box 226, Folder 33)
      - Campaign Advisory Council (Box 226, Folder 34)
      - Campaign in New York City (Box 226, Folder 35)
      - Candidates (Box 227, Folder 36)
      - Center for Political Research (Box 227, Folder 37)
      - Citizens committee (Box 227, Folder 38)
      - Citizen's Union mayoralty election, platform committee recommendations (Box 227, Folder 39)
      - City Hall staff, memoranda (Box 227, Folder 40-41)
      - City Fusion party (Box 227, Folder 42)
      - Civil Service: managerial plan statement JVL, employees newspaper (Box 227, Folder 43)
      - Coalition for community control (Box 227, Folder 44)
      - Computer data firms and campaign consultants (Box 228, Folder 45)
      - Conservative party (Box 228, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence and memoranda (Box 228, Folder 47)
      - County committees meetings (Box 228, Folder 48)
      - Criterion Advertising Co. (Box 228, Folder 49)
      - Daily Mail reports (Box 228, Folder 50)
      - Debates and TV file (Box 228, Folder 51)
      - Department of Personnel Information (Box 228, Folder 52)
      - District leader's list (Box 228, Folder 53)
      - Edward Gottlieb and Associates LTD (Box 228, Folder 54)
      - Election profile (Box 228, Folder 55)
      - Endorsements (Box 229, Folder 56-57)
      - Evans-Novak, political report (Box 229, Folder 58)
      - Fair Campaign Practices committee (Box 229, Folder 59)
      - Field operations, New York Boroughs (Box 229, Folder 60)
      - Finance committee (Box 229, Folder 61)
      - Independent party (Box 229, Folder 62)
      - Independent part petition drive (Box 229, Folder 63)
      - Issues (Box 229, Folder 64)
      - Javits, Jacob K. (Box 229, Folder 65)
      - Jewish Defense League (Box 229, Folder 66)
      - Letters of congratulations (Box 229, Folder 67)
      - Letters to the editor (Box 230, Folder 68)
      - Lists: Citizens committee, Jewish Organizations, PTA presidents (Box 230, Folder 69)
      - Mayor speeches (Box 230, Folder 70)
      - Marchi, John J. (Box 230, Folder 71)
      - Memorabilia, face masks (Box 230, Folder 72)
      - Newark Commercial, protests (Box 230, Folder 73)
      - Patronage by borough (Box 230, Folder 74)
      - Perrotta, Fioravante G.-Garelik, Sanford D. (Box 230, Folder 75)
      - Petty cash records (Box 230, Folder 76)
      - Political biographies (3 copies) (Box 230, Folder 77-78)
      - Poll watchers (Box 230, Folder 79)
      - Primary day, Jun 17 (Box 231, Folder 80)
      - Proaccino, Mario (Box 231, Folder 81)
      - Research (Box 231, Folder 82)
      - Resumes, staff (Box 231, Folder 83)
      - Schedules, JVL (Box 231, Folder 84)
      - Staff (Box 231, Folder 85)
      - Vietnam moratorium (Box 231, Folder 86)
      - Voter registration drive (Box 231, Folder 87)
      - Wagner, Robert F. (Box 231, Folder 88)
    - Subject files, 1970-1972
      - Abandoned buildings (Box 232, Folder 89)
      - Albany office, legislation (Box 232, Folder 90-94)
      - Albany office, legislation (Box 233, Folder 95)
      - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board (Box 233, Folder 96)
      - Art Commission (Box 233, Folder 97)
      - Board of Ethics (Box 233, Folder 98)
      - Budget lines (Box 233, Folder 99)
      - City planning (Box 233, Folder 100)
      - Community boards (Box 233, Folder 101)
      - Community Council of Greater New York (Box 233, Folder 102)
      - Community Development Corporation (Box 233, Folder 103)
      - Construction trades (Box 233, Folder 104)
      - Consumer Advisory Council (Box 233, Folder 105)
      - Convention Visitor's Bureau (Box 233, Folder 106)
      - Corona homeowners, construction of buildings (Box 234, Folder 107-108)
      - Corrections, depatment of (Box 234, Folder 109)
      - Draft deferments (Box 234, Folder 110)
      - Education (Box 234, Folder 111-113)
      - Enviromental Protection Administration (Box 235, Folder 114)
      - Legislative Coordinating Committee (Box 235, Folder 115)
      - Memoranda (Box 235, Folder 116)
      - Mid-term papers on being deputy mayor of New York City (Box 235, Folder 117)
      - Sanitation (Box 235, Folder 118)
      - Task Force (Box 235, Folder 119)
    - Memoranda file, 1971
      - 1971 June 2-July 30 1971 June 2-July 30 (Box 236, Folder 120-123)
      - 1971 August 2-September 15 1971 August 2-September 15 (Box 237, Folder 124-128)
      - 1971 September 16-December 2 1971 September 16-December 2 (Box 238, Folder 129-133)
  - Edward Hamilton (Deputy Mayor), 1969-1973; Series XIII
    Series XIII is sub-divided into two sections:
    Correspondence and Memoranda
    Personnel
    - Correspondence and Memoranda
      - 1969 December-1972 May 1969 December-1972 May (Box 239, Folder 1-6)
      - 1972 June-1973 Dec, undated 1972 June-1973 Dec, undated (Box 240, Folder 7-12)
    - Résumé and memoranda (Box 240, Folder 13)
  - Sid Davidoff (Assistant to the Mayor), 1965-1973; Series XIV; 24 linear feet (57 boxes)
    Series XIV is sub-divided into twelve sections:
    Subject Files, 1965-1969
    Subject Files, 1970-1971
    Administrative Problems
    Neighborhood Problems, 1967-1969
    Summer Job Program, 1967
    Resume File
    Special Requests
    Job Appointments, 1965-1968
    Resumes and Applications, 1966-1971
    Employees in Mayor's Office
    Job Applications, Unsolicited
    - Subject files, 1965-1969
      - Administration improvements, Manhattan (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Aged (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Air pollution (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Agnew, Ted for governor (Box 241, Folder 4)
      - Aides to the mayor (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Anti-draft demonstrations (Box 241, Folder 6)
      - Areas to visit, JVL (Box 241, Folder 7)
      - Artists lofts (Box 241, Folder 8)
      - Atlanta, Martin Luther King funeral (Box 241, Folder 9)
      - Automobiles, acquisition of (Box 241, Folder 10)
      - Bar Association of New York State (Box 241, Folder 11)
      - Bar correspondence (Box 241, Folder 12)
      - Board of Standard and Appeals (Box 241, Folder 13)
      - Bond issue (Box 241, Folder 14)
      - Breakfast meetings (Box 241, Folder 15)
      - Bronx meetings (Box 241, Folder 16)
      - Brooklyn buildings (Box 241, Folder 17-18)
      - Brooklyn Navy Yard (Box 241, Folder 19)